<tp:spec
	xmlns:tp="http://telepathy.freedesktop.org/wiki/DbusSpec#extensions-v0"
	xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude">

<tp:title>SFLphone D-Bus Interface Specification</tp:title>
<tp:version>0.9.8</tp:version>

<tp:copyright>Copyright © 2005-2010 Savoir-faire Linux Inc</tp:copyright>

<tp:license xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<p>This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public
License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
version 2.1 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.</p>

<p>This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
Lesser General Public License for more details.</p>

<p>You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public
License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA.</p>
</tp:license>

<tp:section name="Instances Manager">
 <tp:docstring xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <p>
	An Instance Manager to handle multiple clients connections. Count the number of clients actually registered to the core. When initializing your client, you need to register it against the core by using this interface.
  </p>
 </tp:docstring>
 <xi:include href="instance-introspec.xml"/>
</tp:section>

<tp:section name="Call Manager">
 <tp:docstring xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <p>
	A Call Manager to handle call-related features.
  </p>
 </tp:docstring>
 <xi:include href="callmanager-introspec.xml"/>
</tp:section>

<tp:section name="Configuration Manager">
 <tp:docstring xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <p>
	A Configuration Manager to handle account configuration, user preferences, ...
  </p>
 </tp:docstring>
 <xi:include href="configurationmanager-introspec.xml"/>
</tp:section>

<xi:include href="generic-types.xml"/>

</tp:spec>
